Assassin's Creed 2 is usually considered the best in the series
But what makes it so great and why wasn't unity able to recreate it well I?
Don't care like at all and now for something completely different
Assassin's Creed 2 was of course the first triple-a game to use drm
And that is the actual
Reason piracy doesn't exist anymore when you click start yet to see a quick recap of the previous game
And it's appalling trust me on this one. I know recaps first you play as desmond
I'm sure this is very important, but no one gives a shit
Here's the actual game our main protagonist is [hc] LD taller and right now
He's a spoiled brat Aka typical Assassin, but don't worry this game spans 25 years
So obviously is going to change a lot well
it's going to change lot after the first two years for the
Remaining 23 is going to stay pretty much the same the first part of Ac 2 takes place in Forenza which according to
Wikipedia is a fictional city, but I think it might have been influenced by Florence
And I think that's a pretty neat easter egg
It starts with a tutorial in the first game the tutorial was worse than Trench warfare, but it's way better here you do mundane
Tasks while it introduces you to core characters. There's a [teals] dad and brother named
Ezio's Dad and brother there is his sister salute to claudia and of course Kooky inventor Leonardo da Vinci are not so subtly
reference to Ninja Turtles another difference between the two games is that the first [sasson] screed had like three important characters and
Assassin's Creed 2 [I] lost count around 47 Ezio does a suspicious task first father
But when he returns his father and brothers have been in prison on charges of treason
So he takes a nap I guess and then he visits his father in Prison father
I need money for an iphone. It's you Idiota. Can't you see I'm locked up yes, but you [are] in
To prove his father's innocence
It's you need some documents that are hidden inside the chest he also finds some clothes that he decides to put on
Not sure why that looks great mate he brings the documents to a family friend
[my] father told me to bring these documents to you this yes says I can do whatever I [want] signed. It's yours dad
Yes, can you use the papers to save them sure it's you
I sure can but he doesn't he actually traced the auditory family the sentences the three to death and it's you screams revealing himself
One can only assume that in his last minutes
All you can think was my son is an idiot so it's you manages to escape otherwise. It would be a pretty short game
But to sum it up, assassin's creed [2]. It's an epic revenge story with Moronic AI this is an Assassin's creed game
So you need the hidden blade ubisoft trademark?
So you neither built one for you?
No questions asked [yale] universe inside the can together would be the laboratory devices for fun
Obviously first you kill this guy, then you leave Florence the gang travels to Monteriggioni
But they were followed [by] a guy I forgot to introduce. Oh no, it's you my rival. Yes, it's you it is I
Me now die but they could say but it's your [son] [glue]. That's the same name as an iconic video game character
Who are you? It's you. Don't you recognize me. [it'sa] me Sonic [the] hedgehog then the game goes in Karate
Kid mode where [xe] uncle teaches Ezio about the ways of the assassin your father was innocent [answers] the reason he was
Executed was because he was an assassin way, how can he be innocent if he was a professional killer [ah]?
Yes, but your little brother. Ezio. He was innocent if you go a little brother. Thanks, Ezio
I am selling military secrets to france. [I] guess it's you has to make a choice
Become a kick-ass parkour Assassin with a thirst for vengeance or not Valencia start a brunch place the first target is insert name here
Not sure why though he's an incompetent man child and would make the perfect assassin if you're not familiar with
Assassin's Creed [Loren] timeline it can pretty much be summed up in samplers do something great
Assassin's fucks it up
and then the assassins blame the templar for the fuck up in a sea to the temple controlled by Discolor the
Spaniard as they call him no one knows how he got that name he orders the death of Lorenzo Medici
And you are supposed to rescue him
But I know he dies of natural causes so I decided not to and wouldn't you know it he survives
Then you kill insert names here father you [stalk] his co-conspirator to a secret meeting held by the spaniard okay?
Listen [Canas] we are giving up on flores and focusing on Benezia, and you you're fired
[but] don't worry. We [have] the templars pride ourselves in our fantastic severance package. It's pretty clear that ezio needs to travel to this
Venezia whenever you Defeat an important templar you get the scroll that you give to Leonardo
[then] you get the new ability, but this time he's not there. He's on his way to Valencia. So are we
what a
massive coincidence, but what is [Venecia] really it is get this a
floating city in the 15th century
Yes, I know the assassin's creed games aren't supposed to be realistic, but come on
[but] before you can go to venice you have to play as desmond, and it's kind of boring
[I] hope in future installments. We will instead walk around an office and Dr.
Video game developers actually know what this this is this is fantastic ubisoft never changes this man
Then collapses and we get to play as altair mmM what you see in front of you is the hardest challenge of the entire series
Why would they why would they do this in venice Etsu makes friends with the thieves guild and they put him to work immediately?
[risk] you 12 prisoners elect four guards uniforms in the three thieves Gather ten more guys
travel to ratchet
I say skip all of this and yes to
Dungeons instead the tapes have a target named Emilio [Baba] [Yaga] he wants to unite the merchants of venice this would undoubtedly lead to
lower Crime rates Economic Growth
So obviously we have to kill him because the assassins are assholes now. How could this irrational and insane Decision have any
Consequences well you see the good guys wanted to recruit the doge of venice
But because of x you they panic and decide to kill him instead
They are right there at you not going to attack
Ok ok while you're going through a lot the assassins wants to say the doge
But they can't get into the palace so they come up with the dumbest idea ever
So the doge dies and Ezio spends a week in the hospital
Leonardo I have a piece of paper. Give me a new ability [eat] you I'm sure this 500 year-old weapon is great
But listen what if I just buy you a gun so as you know as a gun
And it's carnival yay
The new Doge is a templar and he just bought crusader kings [-] so he never leaves his house
Except for during carnival where he has to host a party [it] you really wants to go
But you need a golden mask to get in but lucky for him
You can win one by doing tasks like Gather 25 Ribbons collect three flags
Defeat seven opponents and fuck this for joing deadmines you get into the [doge] party and then you shoot him
I'm not even sure why [we] needed to go the mask etsy [has] a fucking gun you kill some other guys
And they tell you that they have given up on venice now
They're going to cyprus on an all-inclusive vacation [two] years later [the] templar come back and they have a mysterious item with them
What could it possibly be [it] just is enclosed and it carries the item to the spaniard who is actually?
Rodrigue a border by the way, there's also this prophecy that a prophet would appear right at this place. Yes this exact
They see the two have this epic true truly epic
Epic sword battle with each other then everyone has helped you throughout the game show up, and they help poor guy escape
Huh, he becomes pope of this, but who was the prophet it was actually the guided Ezio stole the clothes from but now
It's just to take his place
[so] they have to travel to rome and take down pope borja
but this is the PC version of games we have to play through the DLC first if you are on console and
Are thinking about buying the DLC don't the first one can easily be?
Replicated by us running through venice and attacking art and the second [deals] [they] can easily be replicated by going outside and punching a brick
Wall welcome to rome [it's] your face is poor [Jaina] last you will and EtSu can now clone himself
We don't know if this is because of the magical apple or if you'll not you just invent [the] disability not that it matters though
Because it's your has a gun, but haha Rodrigo was only pretending to dead so he stabs that see odin doesn't finish him off
He has runs down a secret passage worst templar ever etsu follows and decides to challenge him to a fistfight
Not the smartest idea, but in his defense
He can't really think straight because he's lost a lot [of] blood obviously he wins etsu has pretty strong arms
He can grab on to stop at terminal velocity [a] door opens and we get to see what rodrigo
Borgia was looking for with this up [prophet]. Who are you? I don't want to speak with you
I want to speak through you to the consumers so I can hike [up] the sequel the sequel
I don't understand okay, basically a couple of thousand [years] ago a bunch of shit happens
But that doesn't really lead anywhere what I'm saying is just by Brotherhood
It's pretty fucking fantastic the rest is up to you
Ubisoft and that's how it ends with a [mindfuck], and so would [I] but I couldn't come up with anything
And that is the killing experience if your login to youtube would you kindly like?
Next video is going to take three [weeks] because I'm very busy [I] wish to speak with you
I want to speak through you am I getting paid for this hmM. No well then you can get the fuck off my island